

CONTACT

(575) 921 1344

https://www.linkedin.com/in/bondcsm/

https://github.com/bondj89

Nob Hill, ABQ, 87106

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF LIBERAL ARTS

2015

University of New Mexico Albuquerque, NM

SKILLS

- Conflict Resolution
- Customer Service
- Documentation Organization
- Microsoft Office Suite
- Project Management
- QA Manual Testing
- Java Programming
- Android Programming

TOOLS

- Salesforce
- Jira
- Trello
- Github
- Microsoft Office
- Vision
- Scrum

JOEL BOND

SAFe 4 Certified Scrum Master / Business Analyst

ABOUT

A results-driven Certified Scrum Master and Technical Business Analyst with over 5 years of experience supporting and managing enterprise solutions for government systems, education, research, and IT organizations. Experienced with leading and providing project and people management, software testing, alongside strategic process awareness and improvements for public and private customers.

EXPERIENCE

BUSINESS ANALYST

New Mexico Department of Health | Santa Fe, NM | June 2019 - Current | Contract

Hired on as a consultant to provided project management and business analysis. My primary focus is to provide a Discovery of current asset and inventory policies in place and to provide an alternative solution better suited for enterprise asset and inventory management. (See LinkedIn for more information)

SCRUM MASTER / BUSINESS ANALYST

RHT Consultant: Presbyterian Health Services | ABQ, NM | Jan 2019 - June 2019 | Contract

Developed and built knowledge across the project lifecycle including scope definition, business case development, requirements gathering, functional and technical design, vendor assessment, testing, training, and implementation phases. Responsible for the planning and facilitation of standard scrum ceremonies to include; backlog preparation, iteration planning, retrospectives, iteration reviews and daily stand-ups.

PROJECT MANAGER

Advanced Network Management | Albuquerque, NM | July 2018 - Jan 2019 | Contract

A customer-focused Project Manager/Scrum Master with a passion to drive process, consistency and communication to meet customer retention and satisfaction goals within an assigned account (client) portfolio. Assumed primary responsibility for coordination and communication on all assigned projects including development and monitoring of project plans, work schedules, status reports, and other deliverables.

BUSINESS ANALYST / PROJECT COORDINATOR

Agile Group USA | Albuquerque, NM | Nov 2016 - July 2018 | Contract

Provided support and training life cycle support for USACE PROMIS (P2) Training Program and specialized in removing impediments for continuous delivery. Defined and communicated product roadmaps with the executive team and business partners. Assisted project managers and instructors in coordinating publications including training manuals, rosters, and other supporting training. DOD Cleared.